<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Return-to-libc</title>
    <link>https://return-to-libc.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Return-to-libc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://return-to-libc.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flash Dell Perc H200 IT mode</title>
      <link>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/dell-h200-it-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/dell-h200-it-mode/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m building a small rack, and right now I&amp;rsquo;m finishing my 2U backup server (I have to show you a picture when everything is ready)&amp;hellip; I got a Dell Perc H200 controller and my idea was to switch it to IT mode to be able to do the raid directly on the OS.
And what an odyssey!
After reading different tutorials, I realised that either the steps were missing, or they were in the wrong order, or it didn&amp;rsquo;t work in UEFI mode (hello 21st century).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LXC USB Passthrough with hot-plug</title>
      <link>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/lxc-usb-passthrough-hot-plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/lxc-usb-passthrough-hot-plug/</guid>
      <description>LXC USB Passthrough with hot-plug in Proxmox. Hello everyone.
I found this post that gave me the key to solve the hot-plug USB under LXC containers.
First of all, under /var/lib/lxc/&amp;lt;ct id&amp;gt;/ create the folder devices, go in and then execute this:
mknod -m 666 ttyACM0 c 166 0
In my case, ttyACM0 is my USB device (my Ender 3 printer). The second number 166 must be the same that you obtain if executed:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install HP AMS on Ubuntu Focal 20.04 LTS</title>
      <link>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/hp-ams-install-in-ubuntu-focal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 19:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/hp-ams-install-in-ubuntu-focal/</guid>
      <description>I have an HP ML310e gen8 that I bought on Ebay a few months ago. I love it!
But this is a bit old server, which already has a few years on the market and that HP no longer provides support. So I&amp;rsquo;m finding some problems.
In this case, I wanted to install HP AMS to improve the ILO more information about the system.
Browsing through the software repository, I found that Focal no longer supported hp-ams, but the previous version Bionic did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable promiscuous mode in VMware Workstation</title>
      <link>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/disable-promiscuous-mode-in-vmware-workstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/disable-promiscuous-mode-in-vmware-workstation/</guid>
      <description>How to disable promiscuous mode in VMware Workstation Hello everyone.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo;. I hope to be more active from now on&amp;hellip;
To disable the promiscuous mode of some of the interfaces of our vm the first thing is to turn it off. Then we look for the associated VMX file. We open it with our favorite text editor and add the following (Replace %d with the interface number):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://return-to-libc.com/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Return-to-libc Hello everyone and welcome to the Return-to-libc blog.
This blog was created with the objetive of sharing and learning computer security knowledge.
Stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
